Every student brings
something unique to the world.
Their interests, their
strengths, their dreams.
Each one of them
represents a future
that really can change
life for all of us.
And when it comes
to their education.
They deserve our very best.
So they can achieve
their very best.
At Pearson, that's what
we've stood for since 1836.
To empower students
to make the most
of their learning experience and
realize their full potential,
we must first be able to assess
their educational journey.
Confidently.
With clarity and focus.
At any step, and at
every step along the way.
That's what our assessments
deliver
to the educational
institutions and leaders
with whom we partner
across the globe.
Clarity, flexibility, and focus.
From assessments of
day-to-day and yearly learning
to ensure college
and career readiness,
To clinical assessments
that help us understand why
students struggle in or out
of the classroom, To developing
customized testing content
that aligns with your
distinct standards,
To enhancing technology,
fostering English
language proficiency,
modernizing assessment
tools, and exploring new ways
to meet the needs of learners
with cognitive disabilities,
Pearson leads the way, and
has for more than a century.
We've written the history
of educational assessments,
and we are shaping its future.
With capabilities
that are global,
but a delivery that's local.
Like you, we know that
it's about outcomes
and putting each student
in a position to succeed
in learning, and in life.
We understand that
no goal is too big,
and no project is too small.
And we know that when it comes
to the future of your students,
you need a partner
you can trust.
A partner who understands
the power of potential
and that everyone's educational
journey is different.
A partner who believes
in your students,
who knows the positive impact
they can have on your economy,
and who is dedicated to helping
you achieve the best possible
outcomes no matter how
challenging the economic
environment may be.
Because in the end,
We're always learning.